>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有一种相信的诱惑，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is
a temptation to believe, and
这在社会上是一种邪教的感觉
it's sort of a cult feeling
among the community,
大多数开发者倾向于认为隐含机制是神奇的。
most developers tend to think that
implicit mechanisms are magical.
当某些事情发生在幕后的时候，这并不是显而易见的，
That when something happens underneath
the scenes, and it wasn't obvious,
那就像魔术一样
then it's some sort of magic.
我们倾向于把魔法等同于邪恶邪恶
And we tend to equate magic with bad,
evil,
这不太好因为我不明白发生了什么
like this is not good because I
can't understand what's happening.
这也是反胁迫的主要原因
And this is a predominant reason
why that anti-coercion prospective
存在是因为人们觉得胁迫的暗示就是
exists is because people feel like the
implicitness of coercion is the downfall
在 Java 或 C++的情况下，它们指向类型转换的解释。
where they point to explicitness of type
casting in something like Java or C++.
然后他们说
And then they say,
你永远不会自动把整数转换为浮漂什么的
you would never automatically convert
an integer into a float or whatever.
但 JavaScript 会做这些自动的事情然后他们说
But JavaScript does all this sort of
automatic stuff and then they say, well,
这就是 JavaScript 的弱点因为它是魔幻和糟糕的
that's a weakness of JavaScript
because it's magical and bad.
我觉得这不是件事
I don't think it's either of those things,
我认为我们应该考虑这个抽象的概念。
I think that we should think about
implicitness as abstraction.
并非所有抽象都是好的，但某些抽象是必需的。
Not all abstractions are good, but
some abstractions are necessary.
很复杂，我们不在这里处理功能性编程。
Implicitness, and we're not dealing
with functional programming here.
这不是当然，这是不同的课程。
This is not this course,
that's a different course.
这是一个插头，你可以检查我的功能编程课程。
Here's a plug, you can check on
my functional programming course.
但在功能编程中，您可以在整个位置使用抽象。
But within functional programming,
you use abstraction all over the place.
事实证明，声明形式的编码实际上更含蓄。
And it turns out that the declarative
style of coding is actually more implicit.
因此，牵连的问题并不严重，是适当的障碍。
So implicitness is not bad,
it is the proper usage of obstruction.
换句话说，我们想隐藏一些不必要的细节，为什么 ?
In other words, we want to hide
key unnecessary details, why?
因为重新把读者的注意力放在重要的东西上。
Because that re-focuses the reader
on the important stuff.
我们不会用他们不需要的东西来分散他们的注意力。
We're not distracting them with
the stuff that they don't need.
我们想集中注意力
We wanna focus them.
我们想通过重新聚焦来提高代码的清晰度。
We wanna increase the clarity
of the code by re-focusing.
因此， JavaScript 类型系统的某些隐式性质是粗略的，
So some of the implicit nature of
JavaScript's type system is sketchy,
但其中有些很有用
but some of it is quite useful.
比如说拳击赛
For example, the boxing.
那是隐含的，但也很有用，因为要分散
That's implicit, but also very useful,
because the distraction of having to
把它变成一个物体，我在大多数情况下会说，
cast it into an object isn't,
what I would argue in most cases,
读者不需要的不必要的详细信息。
an unnecessary detail that
the reader doesn't need.
而这实际上是在 JavaScript的 DNA 中。
And that's actually at
the DNA of JavaScript.
部分原因 JavaScript 具有这样的低壁垒
Part of the reason JavaScript
has such a low barrier to entry
因为它不强制读者去处理一堆不必要的细节。
is because it doesn't force the reader to
deal with a bunch of unnecessary detail.
它背叛了 JavaScript的 DNA 暗示所有这些
It betrays JavaScript's DNA to
suggest that all those implicit
事情是我们应该避免的
things are things that we should avoid.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在这里，如果我用字串来让它变得很明显
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So here, if I'm writing
string to make it super obvious that I'm
把这件事变成一个字符串我不知道我觉得这很分散
gonna make this thing into a string,
I don't know, I think that's distracting.
我想我会把电话里的号码
I think I would just
drop in the number and
因为我知道那个号码在任何一个角落都没有
be perfectly happy, because I know that
number is never in any of those corner
有些事情可能会很奇怪
cases where something could be weird.
也许我已经检查过，比如说，那些学生不是男学生。
Maybe I've already checked to make sure
that num students is not nan, for example.
所有其他数字可能除了负零以外
All the other numbers that it could
possibly be other than negative zero and
尼恩这是我唯一需要担心的地方
nan, those are my only corner cases
that I need to worry about here.
那么，如果我有处理这些角落案件的声明，那么这一行
So if I have if statements that deal with
those corner cases, then this line of
代码行 4 是更有效的沟通
code, line 4, is actually better
communication, cuz it properly lets
JavaScript 抽象详细信息，无需在该时刻处理。
JavaScript abstract the detail that's not
necessary to deal with at that moment.
这是另一个例子，不是运营商，
Here's another example,
the less than operator,
我们讨论了如何将事情变成数字
we talked about how it
coerces things into numbers.
有时候你想
Sometimes you wanna go ahead and
确保两者都是数字这样你就不会觉得奇怪了
make sure that both of them are a number
so that you don't get something weird.
例如，如果两者都是字符串，那么不会将两者都转换为数字。
For example, if both of them are strings,
it doesn't turn them both into numbers.
小于运算符可进行字母数字比较。
The less than operator does
an alphanumeric comparison.
这里有个角箱如果你能用不到两条
So there's a corner case, if you could
possibly have a less than applied to two
你最好先确定他们都是号码
strings, you probably do wanna make
sure that they're both numbers first.
但如果我在密码的地方我知道其中至少有一个是
But if I'm in a place of the code
where I know at least one of them is
一定是号码吗
definitely a number?
那我就知道另一个会变成数字了也许不是
Well then, I know the other one's gonna
become a number, so maybe it's not
强迫你解读我让他们俩都是数字的事实
necessary to force you to read the fact
that I'm making them both numbers.
也许还可以，让这比经营者的方式少得多。
Maybe it's okay, to let that less
than operator do the coercion form.
这些不是艰难和快速的规则
These are not hard and fast rules,
这些都是想训练你这样想分析
these are trying to train you
to think like this to analyze.
如果你在一个你可以选择使用胁迫的地方
And if you are in a place where you
have the choice to use coercion but
不明显这在你的权限范围内是显而易见的
it's not obvious, it's within
your purview to make it obvious.
很明显他们都是号码
Make it obvious that
they're both numbers and
所以我不需要担心明确地铸造它们。
therefore, I don't need to worry
about explicitly casting them.
很明显他们都是数字
It's just already obvious
that they're both numbers.
如果你传达了这个意图，它就不会让其他的读者去旅行了。
If you communicate that intent, it's not
gonna trip up other readers of the code.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 真的，问题是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Really, the question is,
是否向读者显示这些额外的详细信息 ?
is showing these extra details
helpful to the reader or not?
有时是，有时是不。
Sometimes yes, sometimes no.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 基本上，我要求你做重要的分析思考者，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Basically, I'm asking
you to be critical, analytical thinkers,
做工程师而不是密码猴子好吗
to be an engineer and
not a code monkey, okay?